LGBTQ Ephemera Collection, 1964-1992 and undated RL.10183
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
LGBTQ ephemera collection
1964-1992 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
RL.10183
1.5 Linear Feet
The LGBTQ (Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, Transgender, and Queer) Ephemera Collection consists of pamphlets, flyers, t-shirts, and other items that document homosexual and alternative sexualities in the United States.
Collection Overview
The LGBTQ Ephemera Collection includes posters, pamphlets, newsletters, t-shirts, and other miscellany from a range of organizations and events. Most items are foldered individually with titles listed below.
Provenance
The LGBTQ Ephemera Collection was acquired piecemeal by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, beginning in 2012.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Gay pride celebrations; Gay and lesbian rights; Lesbian activists -- United States; Homosexuality and education -- United States; AIDS (Disease) -- Prevention; Transgenderism; Transgender people -- United States
- Susan Saxe Poster, undated (Folder 1)
- Book Abstract: "Who Is a Homosexual?" by C.A. Tripp, PhD, 1965 (Box 1)
- The Tangent Group membership letter, undated (Box 1)
- East Coast Homophile Organization conference proceedings, 1964 (Box 1)
- Cincinnati Homophile Organization informational handout, undated (Box 1)
- Nebraska Pluralism Council informational booklet, undated (Box 1)
- Association for Social Knowledge newsletter, 1967 June (Box 1)
- Coalition for Human Rights tri-fold brochure, undated, ca. 1977 (Box 1)
- Miscellaneous pamphlets and handouts for Pride Rallies, 1981-1992 (Box 1)
- Pride t-shirt, undated (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Gift of Steven Adams.
- "God is greater than AIDS" t-shirt, undated (Box 1)
- Program for original play: "The Sweetest Hangover (and other STDs)", undated (Box 1)
- The Dyke Sex Calendar, 1990 (Box 1)
- "Be All You Want to Be:" Transexual Seminar Programs brochure, Cleveland, 1991 (Box 1)